let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How many Hidden Villages in the Naruto Series?",
    answer: "5",
    options: ["10", "7", "5", "8"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the Name of the Rival of Naruto?",
    answer: "Sasuke Uchiha",
    options: ["Neiji Hyuga", "Sasuke Uchiha", "Rock Lee", "Kankuro"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who is from Namikaze Clan?",
    answer: "Minato",
    options: ["Lady Tsunade", "Hiruzen", "Minato", "Naruto"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who created rasengan?",
    answer: "Minato",
    options: ["Minato", "Hiruzen", "Kushina", "Naruto"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the Forbidden Jutsu that Naruto uses?",
    answer: "Multy Shadow Clone Jutsu",
    options: [
      "Multy Shadow Clone Jutsu",
      "Teleportation Jutsu",
      "Water Clone Jutsu",
      "Harem Jutsu",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who perfectly uses Teleportation Jutsu?",
    answer: "Minato Namikaze",
    options: [
      "Hiruzen Saratobi",
      "Tobirama Senju",
      "Naruto Uzumaki",
      "Minato Namikaze",
    ],
  },


  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many members are there in Akatsuki?",
    answer: "12",
    options: ["10", "11", "15", "12"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many beasts are there in the Naruto Series?",
    answer: "9",
    options: ["10", "7", "9", "8"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "When kakashi showed his Sharingan for the First time?",
    answer: "Battle Against Zabusa",
    options: [
      "Battle Against Zabusa",
      "Battle against Itachi",
      "Battle against Obito",
      "Battle against Kakuzu",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who perfectly mastered the 8 tails ?",
    answer: "Killer B",
    options: ["Killer B", "A", "Mito", "Haku",],
  },
];